[SOUND] So in this module we're going to
[声音] 在这个模块中 我们将要学习
be looking at visualization systems.
可视化系统
So before we do that, we should nail down some concepts.
在这之前 我们需要再理清一些概念
And so there's going to be several concepts that we'll need to review and
介绍和回顾这些可视化系统的概念
introduce on these visualization systems that'll be helpful.
将对你有所帮助
The first one we've seen before is information visualization.
首先 第一个概念是我们已经讲过的信息可视化
We've used that as a term to describe the plotting of data
信息可视化 通常是指
that uses different coordinates than what was provided.
使用与已有坐标不同的坐标来绘制数据
In information visualization as opposed to scientific visualization or
信息可视化与科学可视化 或者其他领域里的一些可视化不同
other domain visualization where the data comes to you in a more concrete metaphor,
后者的数据可以给人比较具体的象征
information visualization the information is much more abstract, and so
而信息可视化中 需要被可视化的信息则抽象的多
the challenge is going to be being able to take that abstract information and
所以 它的难点在于 如何从抽象的信息中
find a concrete metaphor to communicate it to the viewer, so
找到具象的表达方式 并将它传达给读者
it can be more easily understood.
使人们能更简单的理解这些信息
The second is large data visualization.
第二个概念是大数据可视化
We often hear of big data and there's also big data visualization.
大数据现在是时下的热词 随之而来的便是大数据可视化
The focus of big data or large data visualization is sometimes just on
大数据可视化的一部分重点在于
the computation mechanics of handling large data sets.
处理大数据集的计算方法
But we're going to focus specifically on the visualization of large data, where
但我们这门课程将特别聚焦于大数据的可视化部分
the data is so large that it's visually overwhelming if you display everything,
因为数据量非常大 所以如果把所有的数据都展示出来 呈现的可视化结果会令人感到无所适从
and so you have to be very selective about what you display so
所以 要对需要被展现的数据进行精心的选择
that you can keep it mentally organized.
这样才可以在思维中组织起来
And so, we're going to depend on interactivity, the interactive aspect
而要实现这点 就需要依赖系统的交互性 系统的可交互
of these visualization system to be able to, over time,
可以使可视化系统由始至终
focus on certain elements of our visualization that we're interested in,
聚焦于我们感兴趣的某些元素
and to be able to ignore other elements so that these data sets,
并忽略那些数据集中我们不感兴趣的其他内容 （这些内容往往非常大）
which would be very large, don't overwhelm our cognitive understandings.
这样一来 我们就能对可视化结果有清晰的认知理解
Third is visual analytics, visual analytics is an area that grew out of
第三个概念是视觉分析 视觉分析是从
business analytics and business intelligence, and
商务分析和商务智能衍生出来的领域
it's specifically on visualization, being able to look at data sets visually and
它聚焦于使数据集可视化 并且
to be able to analyze them, draw conclusions from them,
能对数据集进行分析 并得出分析结果
and it focuses also on being able to make a decision based on data and
同时 它的另一个重点是 基于数据做出决策
that decision is implied by the visualization, that the visualization
可视化系统能够让人们
is giving you the insight in order to make a good decision based on your data.
对数据有深入的了解 从而能基于数据来制定正确的决策
And finally the goal of this week is to make a visualization dashboard.
最后一点 本周的学习目标是 制作一个可视化系统的管理面板
We want to be able to organize the visualizations when we have multiple
当我们有多个可视化任务 或者我们有非常多的数据的时候
visualizations and we have a lot of data.
我们希望能将这些可视化任务和数据组织起来
We'll want to be able to produce a dashboard view that gives you everything
我们希望能有个管理面板视图 在这个视图中能提供
you need in order to be able to make a good decision based on the data.
用户所需的所有数据 并能帮助其作出好的决策
So those are some of the terms,
好了，以上就是今天讲的几点概念
some of the main concepts we use when we talk about visualization system.
这些主要的概念是当我们讲可视化系统时要用到的
We start with information visualization but our goal for
我们从信息可视化开始讲起 一直到我们本周的学习目标
the week is going to be to understand how to make a visualization dashboard,
如何制作一个可视化系统的管理面板
how to make a visualization system that we can use to make decisions
以及如何实现一个能为人们提供决策的可视化系统
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community